Ice cream!
All right.
all right. all right.
Who got money?
Yo. you got some money. huh?
Hey. hey. hey!
-Hey!
-Come on. let's go.
Hold it.
Come here. Come here.
Where y'all going. huh?
Get off me. Franklin!
Ow. my neck!
Drop it.
and I'll let you go.
Ow!
Let us go. Franklin!
Come on. Franklin. What the hell?
What's it gonna be?
Let go!
Get out of here.
Yeah.
y'all better run.
I see you again.
I'll beat that ass.
Ah. ease up. playboy.
You got your 50 cents
of shit back.
You're welcome.
They call me Mr. Tibbs.
Uh-oh. Neighborhood Watch
in the house.
Why-oh.
Black Magnum P.I. lookin'.
What.
you a narc now. cuz?
Nah. man.
punks were stealing candy.
Shit. nigga.
I used to steal candy.
Mm-hmm. Look how
your ass turned out.
So why you care
if some little kids
is running off
with some Ring Pops. man?
They got to learn.
-That ain't how America work.
-Says who?
Hey. cuz.
spot me a cone. though.
Spot your mama a cone.
Spot your mama a cone. nigga.
What you runnin' for?
-Ghetto Jackson 5 lookin'...
-Spot your mama. though.
Hey. hey. man!
Come here!
Flip that.
flip that.
Yeah. Oso. get up!
Oso!
That's what
I'm talking about. man.
Let's go!
Yeah!
That's right. Oso!
That's
my dawg right there.
Oso...box.
Fight. man.
That's what you get.
Come on.
Let's go!
One. two. three!
Man. this is bullshit.
Pay up. You. too. Leon.
Pay up. fool.
You all right?
Looks like that white boy
tuned you up pretty good.
Maybe I should
hire him instead.
I keep telling Pedro it's fake.
but he won't listen.
That shit
look fake to you?
Huh?
My cousin... Lucia.
Talks too much.
Mucho gusto.
El Oso?
Oh. man!
I knew that was you!
Uh. you don't think
I could. like.
get an autograph
or something?
Easily impressed.
huh. kid?
-You have a pen?
-Um. nah. I don't.
Here. I do.
All right. cool.
Thanks. man.
Nice to meet you.
You know we ain't here
for an autograph. right?
Just give me the name
and the address of the Vato.
and how much they owe.
We don't need you
to collect this time.
We've got something else.
Higher risk.
but you pull it off.
we'll bring you on
full-time.
That's what you wanted.
right?
Hmm?
Be part of the family?
This stuff is.
like. amazing.
My heart's beating
like a bunny rabbit's.
Feel it.
Do it.
Okay. do it.
Come on. come on!
Come on!
Oh! Oh!
Aah! Oh!
Ale. you got to try
this shit. man.
I want to see.
The only thing
you'll see in there
is a grown man
with a straw in his ass.
Oh. my God!
Alejandro!
Call an ambulance!
What's the matter with you?
Call an ambulance.
Fuck!
Please leave a message
after the tone.
Hey. it's me.
I thought I might catch you
on your lunch break.
I'm at the office.
I'll be here. uh.
watching the clock.
if. uh. you get a minute.
I got to go. All right. bye.
This Aero Services Aviation?
How can I help you?
You Teddy?
Teddy McDonald?
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
A friend
of Logan Miller.
He said if there
was ever a problem.
you were the man to see.
I guess that means
there's a problem.
I need you to take
a ride with me. Teddy.
You can bring the gun if it
makes you more comfortable.
What's up. Franklin?
What's up?
What's up. y'all?
-Hey. Jerome.
-What's up. Mike?
What's up?
What's up. nephew?
Damn. everybody getting wet
on that sherm. huh?
Sell it.
don't smoke it...
I tell myself that shit
every day.
Peace out.
You're looking real scrawny.
nephew.
Need to get
your weight up.
And strengthen the mind.
Yeah.
Say what up
to your auntie.
She still
ain't working?
What's up. Aunt Louie?
Nephew!
Now. you know I love you.
but right now.
this Luke and Laura shit.
I-I just can't.
Luke and Laura.
I'm sorry
I picked up the wrong one.
Louie. that boy
don't care two shits
about none of that
nonsense.
Kiss my ass. Jerome.
Hey.
Cissy still don't know nothing
about this. right?
Man. hell no.
If your mama find out.
that'd be both our ass.
-Bye.
-Goodbye. darling.
Mm-hmm.
Mind if I bag this up
right here?
Do your thing.
You see
your pops lately?
Nope.
Jerome!
Bring your black ass
out here!
Jerome.
I know you in there!
So sick and tired of you.
Hey. bitch.
you out your goddamn mind.
come up to my house acting a fool! Get
your black ass out here and talk to me!
Jerome. you better
shut that bitch up
while I'm watching my stories.
I mean it. Jerome!
Jerome. I
need to talk to you!
Get away from my door.
Told you not to fuck that girl
without me. Now look at you.
Jerome. I think you forget about
how much I know about you.
All I know is
you better get your ass home
before you get dealt with.
-What you gon' do?
Look.
I'm-a give you to five.
Five. four. three. two. one.
What?
Hey. come beat this bitch ass.
I ain't got no time for this.
Get your black ass out here and talk to me.
Louie! Louie!
Jerome! Jerome!
Louie. come out here
and deal with this!
Oh. so now you're gonna call somebody?
Come... I ain't got no time for this shit.
Come deal with this bitch.
Why don't you handle your shit
like a man?
Fine!
She gonna stick on you.
Shit!
-Bitch!
-Get off of me!
Get the fuck off.
would you?!
What I tell you? Damn!
Get the fuck up!
Get off of me. ho!
Damn.
Look at your auntie.
She's a wild cat...
and she turn me on.
Mm. Mm.
All right.
Cool place.
It's not mine.
This way.
Put your
hands on your head.
Relax.
I am relaxed.
Please put your hands
on your head.
We were celebrating.
He overdid it.
And what'd you do...
say a prayer?
Why didn't you call
an ambulance?
It'll be easier
if I just show you.
Slow.
Now you see why
I didn't call an ambulance.
Alejan...
It's Alejandro...right?
Who are you?
How do you know Logan Miller?
Why does
a dead CIA officer
have a mountain of cocaine
in a hot tub?
Are you hungry?
Do you mind?
I know how
it sounds. but this is real.
What you saw is the first load
of many to come.
Real? This... You do understand
that the company isn't even
supposed to be operating on U.S.
soil. don't you? Aren't you?
-That's a little different.
-How?
'Cause I manage foreign assets
living in Los Angeles.
-So was Logan.
-Oh. you're being cute?
No. Would you please...
put out the cigarette?
Logan said you'd help me.
All right. well. I've got
bad news for you. Alejandro.
I barely knew
Logan Miller.
Well. he knew you...
said you were a hammerhead.
a patriot
who hated communism.
This plan... this is Logan's or yours?
Logan's.
And were you partying with him
last night?
Using. I mean?
Or was it just him?
Why does it matter?
I don't know.
Maybe Logan Miller
woke up yesterday.
looked at 50 kilos' worth of
cocaine hidden in a hot tub.
remembered that Miami was just
on the cover of Time magazine
and Nancy Reagan's out there
telling anyone who will listen
to "Just say no."
he decides to pull the plug.
and that doesn't work
for you.
Your government
came to my country.
organized us. trained us.
encouraged us to fight.
And then one day. your Congress
just changed its mind.
I understand that.
Do you understand
that right now
there are literally thousands
of soldiers in the jungle
waiting for me to deliver
supplies and weapons?
They are hungry and sick.
and if I fail.
they will die.
Do you honestly think that this
is the best way to help them?
Yes.
But I'm a soldier.
not a drug dealer.
I can't run this operation
without the support of the CIA.
So if you're not the officer
who can help me.
please direct me
to who is.
How you choose
Kraft over Velveeta.
I will never understand.
Mm.
How you doing?
What happened?
Oh.
Don't worry about that.
Somebody put their hands
on you?
Thought Tulf was gonna hook you
up with them Westside properties.
get you out
of all this bullshit.
He's working on it.
Working on it.
Come sit with me
a minute.
Lee and Kev
waitin' on me.
They can wait.
You work today?
Tomorrow.
Called up there this morning.
told Cho I'm not coming.
You out
of your cowboy mind?
How you gonna tell that man when
you're gonna work at his business?
"Out of my cowboy mind"?
What does that mean?
Franklin.
Unh-unh.
It ain't for you.
You just got home.
Saint residence.
Yes. sir. I-I just did.
told her she had two days.
as we discussed.
No. it's...
you're right.
There's no sense
in waiting.
I'll... I'll go back out
first thing
and... and
take care of it.
I'll have
a new tenant in there
within... within
the week.
One that pays on time.
I...
It's my pleasure.
Mr. Tulfowitz.
Have a good night.
Bye-bye.
Don't say it.
I didn't say anything.
You were thinking it.
I was thinking about how good
your white phone voice got.
Hey. if you good.
I'm good.
Hey.
Give me another hug.
Then you can go.
I love you. Franklin.
Love you. too. Mom.
Get some rest.
Move it along. amigo.
Damn.
Hey. what's up. Melody?
Just a cutie pie.
ain't you?
Looking
to catch a beatdown?
-Want some bloodshed?
-No. sir. Mr. Wright.
No. we good. Andre.
"Andre"?
A nigga can't say hi
to nobody?
Say hi to a foot
in your narrow ass.
Hey. so. what we got
up today. Saint?
I got some things
I got to do.
All right.
I'll roll with you. then.
Gonna be a problem?
All right. then.
Hey. man.
turn down the box.
Huh?
They teach you to act different
at the school out here?
Taught me a lot of shit.
What you learn in the juvie?
Taught me how to squab harder.
make a sharper shank.
protect the booty
and not be fruity.
See. I know what I know.
You know what you know. cuz.
Yeah. but you don't really
know nothing. though.
Oh. I don't know nothing?
Nah. man.
Know how to slap the shit out of you.
You crazy.
Hey. don't make me
go butterfly on your...
Hey. guys.
I-I'm sorry.
Would you... Would you mind
turning that down. please?
That better?
Come on. man.
"Come on." what?
You know that dude?
I asked you nicely.
Ask me again. you gonna eat
this motherfucking radio!
Go ahead!
Do it and see what happen!
Hey.
what you moving for?
'Cause you stupid.
Your mama stupid.
Stupid.
Goddamn.
Rob-o!
Yo-o-o!
My brother!
Frankie! Come on! Ah.
Good to see you.
too. man.
Oh!
Ah.
this is my boy Leon.
Leon. Leon. Le... You were
the guy in jail. right?
Juvie.
It's cool. man.
Come on in.
Oh. we're casting today...
well. Dad is.
All right. I need you
and you in front of the camera.
Yeah.
Come on. man.
It's all for you. Leon.
All of this is all yours.
Merry Christmas. Happy Hanukkah.
see you next year.
Hey. Tracy.
Nasty.
Yeah. with her legs.
All right.
Big smiles.
Hey. Frankie.
We miss seeing you
around here.
Hi. Mrs. Volpe.
This is my friend Leon.
-Nice to meet you. Leon.
-Hey. How you doing?
Mom. could you
please wear a robe?
Oh. stop. Robert.
Let me enjoy my last few years
of looking this way.
Are you boys hungry?
Yeah.
I could eat something.
No. we're all right.
but thank you.
Well. help yourself.
Okay.
Well. you know
where to find it.
Okay. okay.
All right.
Hey. stop
checking my man's mom. dude.
Yo. moms
is checking me.
So. Frankie told you he was
prom king at our school. right?
Oh. and best friends
with all the teachers.
No. he didn't hip me
to that info.
Did you. Frankie?
Franklin Saint.
king of all the white boys.
Whoa.
that's some new stuff.
So. my parents are going out
of town this weekend. okay?
So come by.
I miss you. man.
I miss you.
Leon...you're my brother.
too. now.
Come on.
Hey. so. when I move in.
you think Rob will want
to call me Dad or just Leon?
-Lee. shut up.
-No. For real. though.
Why you keeping shit
from the homies. man?
It's like you're living
a whole other life out here.
It was just easier
to stay out here
during the weekdays.
with school and all.
Look at this place.
Why would you ever want
to leave here. loc?
It's cool for a minute.
But it ain't home.
Ought to
mind your shitter. dude.
Like something died
in there.
Did you give him the key.
the alarm code.
tell him where it's at?
Okay.
You do everything
like we said.
you walk in and out
like you own the place.
Once you have the money.
there's gonna be
a voice in your head
telling you
to get in your car
and drive east
until you hit ocean.
and there's nothing
we can do to stop you.
You want to be a part
of our business...
of our family...
the only way that happens
is if we all trust each other.
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
blah. blah. blah.
He knows that
if he tries any bullshit.
I'll hunt him down
and kill his ass.
Ain't that right. Oso?
Ciao. papi.
Good luck.
Hey!
Give me the money.
a bottle of Boone's Farm.
and some Pop Rocks.
fool.
You snuck out.
Andre catch you.
you gonna get a whupping.
Boy at my school having a party.
You want to go?
I am not going
to no high-school party.
You're only
two years older than me.
I got to stay here
and lock up.
Okay.
I'll take that Boone's
to help you out before I go.
So. how come
you don't drink?
I don't know.
Just don't
make me feel good...
...just all tired and slow.
Then what does
make you feel good?
-This.
-Talking to me?
Working. getting paid.
You mean making 3 bucks an hour
riding that mop?
I give you liquor.
and you hit me with attitude.
For real.
what was the point
of you going out to
that fancy school in the Valley
if you was gonna bail on college
and stay around here?
Do you know what I felt in
that fancy school in the Valley?
Like an outsider.
a mascot.
-College gonna be the same shit.
-There's black colleges.
On the other side of the country.
So?
Moms could barely handle it when
I was staying in the Valley.
I ain't leaving her here.
And. look. I'm getting paid
to learn
how to run a business.
Cho don't sweat me.
Rather do things when I want
and how I want
than get paid more at some
office job and eat shit.
That ain't
what I'm after.
Oh. so you are
after something.
Fucking right.
And what's that?
Freedom.
Freedom from all of it.
You know
when I'll feel free?
When I'm somewhere
far off from here.
Franklin. it's Cho. man!
Why my store closed?!
Relax.
This is Cho's store.
not yo' store!
Open up!
That ain't Cho.
Hey. you stupid.
Hey. man. you supposed to be
selling my products!
What you over there playing with. man?
Come on...
Crazy.
I'll kung-fu your ass.
Hey. open the door. man.
Hyah! Y'all know that's
racist as fuck. right?
No. man.
You know what's racist.
is when he pulled that shotgun
on me over them Now and Laters.
-What's up. Melody?
-What's up?
Hey. maybe we should give y'all
some alone time and shit. no?
-Oh!
Alejandro made it sound
like you already knew.
Well. I can see how
it was in Logan's interest
to make it seem
that way.
Is there more?
Yeah. Uh. you don't want
to hear it.
Okay. so. what are we
talking about?
This could
actually work.
It's risk/reward.
How badly does the director
want this war funded?
Have you ever seen
a congressional hearing?
They are no fun
for anybody.
That won't happen.
No?
No. not if you
let me run it.
You really think you're the guy
to step into this?
Uh. yeah.
I think I'm the perfect guy.
Look. it goes wrong.
we tell them I had a breakdown.
I went off the reservation.
all right?
My file supports that story.
and the agency stays clean.
They would absolutely
crucify you. Teddy.
We both know
why you sent me out here.
It was banishment
disguised as a favor.
I want
back in the game.
I am 28 years old.
James.
I am not ready to be done
with this life.
Please.
Whoo!
Franklin.
come have some of this.
I'm cool.
Thank you.
Give me one second.
So. I got
a favor to ask.
What's up?
The thing is. that was
the last of my parents' coke.
And my girl
really likes it.
I ain't never
scored blow before.
I know a guy.
He's my parents' dealer. but...
But what?
He's kind of crazy.
You mean you afraid
to go get it.
So send the black guy.
right?
I'm playing with you. man.
I'll be the black guy. Shit.
I'm always the black guy.
All right.
So. this guy's
legitimately insane.
so just get in.
get out.
That was probably
from another house.
Don't be a baby.
It didn't even
break the skin.
-You all right?
-I'm coming to see. Relax.
Avi.
-Avi.
-Huh?
Volpe?
The Volpe kid sent you here
because he's afraid?
He's a pussy.
He all right?
No.
he's not "all right."
Just shot him.
What do you want?
Uh. I-I'm here to buy.
I don't sell coke to kids.
I ain't a kid.
I got the money.
I definitely don't sell
$200 worth of coke.
Then what do you sell?
I sell kilos
to people with money.
Now go. scram.
Okay. front me a key...
...and I'll
turn it around quick.
Huh? How you plan
on doing that?
I know people...
people in my neighborhood.
They don't even know what
cocaine is in your neighborhood.
let alone have the money
to afford it.
My people do.
It could mean a whole new
client base for you.
a whole new...
revenue stream.
You know
some fancy words.
Doesn't mean
you're not full of shit.
How can I convince you
I'm for real?
Show me.
Farther you are.
harder it is
for me to aim true.
Closer you are.
the more it hurts.
Shitty choices.
Welcome
to the real world.
Any last words.
just in case?
Don't miss.
You got balls. kid.
I give you that.
Come here.
How do I know you're not just
gonna take my kilo and disappear?
Stealing from you gets me
a one-time payday
and a lifetime
of looking over my shoulder.
But if I move the key
and bring you back the cash.
then I got a friend
for life.
You got one day
to bring me $12.000.
One day?
H-H-How am I
supposed to cut it.
weigh it. bag it.
sell it.
and bring you back your cash
in one day?
Not my problem.
You say
you have the market?
Show me.
Here.
Give this
to pussy boy.
-Send him home.
-He my ride.
No.
My guys are your ride.
That way.
I know where you live.
See you tomorrow.
Frankie.
Otherwise.
I'll see you after that.
Aah!
Hello?
Hey. It's me.
Oh. Hey.
Sorry.
Did I wake him up or...?
Um. no.
Looks like we're okay.
How are you?
Is everything all right?
Yeah.
No. I'm... I'm good.
I. uh...I just really wanted
to hear your voice.
A.
So... And thank you for.
uh. sending the pictures and...
Oh. yeah. sur.
...the tape. and. um...
Of course.
It just makes me feel like I'm
not missing so much. you know?
Mm. I'm really glad.
Hey. James said he saw you
and that an officer was killed.
-Oh. he did?
-Mm-hmm.
He made it sound like maye
your exile was
about to get interestin.
- Is something...
Oh. shi.
-Yeah.
-Hold on.
-I spoke too soon.
I'm gonna have
to call you back. oka?
Okay. Yeah. Well. but I'm not...
I'm not at...
I've got to... Mnh.
Her sherm-smoking ass
ain't waking up no time soon.
Whatever you got to say.
spit it out.
Boy. you know. I'm in
the weed-and-water business.
What you doing
with that much coke?
Franklin. I don't need nobody
coming to my house looking for...
Relax. Unc.
I got a new friend.
You got a connect?
That's right.
And he just fronted you
a bird of coke?
Who you dealing with. nephew?
Ain't nobody black.
I told him
I'd turn it around fast.
Got till tomorrow to make good.
Tomorrow? Where the hell...
How you gonna get a key of coke
off in 24 hours around here?
Ugh. What's up?
-Hey. baby.
-What y'all doing?
You been in the game
for a while.
Got to know somebody
who could afford it.
I figure we could split the profits.
You figure?
Big boy.
you gon' come in my house
and tell me what I'm-a get?
-This is business. Unc.
I'm trying to make
some real money here.
I-I thought
you'd want to be down.
Man. money ain't nothing
but paper with them
crackers' faces on it.
And that brick...
that ain't worth the trouble
that it come with.
I promise you. man.
No. look...
I tried to do shit
the right way.
went to the other side.
Know what I learned?
The game's rigged.
It ain't made for people
like us. so you know what?
I'm rewriting the rules.
But. Unc.
I need your help to do it.
Huh?
Not this time. nephew.
Go on. man.
Get out of my house. man.
Shit out of my house.
...the National
Guard has been contacted.
The governor did not say
if he would actually
call out the Guard.
Baby. you good?
Yeah. Mom.
Get some sleep.
Unemployment declined by...
You sure it's real?
And Logan wouldn't
have been stupid enough
to run this himself.
I mean. he must have been
using other assets.
If he was.
I didn't know them.
So... Okay. and who
were you dealing with?
Aside from my people.
the customs guys at Hawthorne
and the Israeli distributor.
And what about
the Mexicans?
That was Logan.
Why them?
What?
The girl Lucia...
he wanted to sleep with her.
but she wouldn't let him.
You're surprised?
The only thing he liked more than
cocaine and America was pussy.
All right.
I have to meet with everyone.
You just said it'd be stupid
to run this yourself.
Well. once I can vet them
and decide who we can trust
and replace the ones we can't.
then I step away.
These contacts are
comfortable with me.
You show up
and start asking questions.
they'll get nervous.
especially Avi.
This is what I do.
Alejandro.
It'll be fine.
I'm completely covered.
yes?
Something goes wrong
and I get arrested.
you make your calls
and I get walked out of jail?
Yeah.
You're covered.
Oh. hey. uh.
one more thing.
You said that there was
no one here besides you
when Logan O.D.'d. right?
-That's right.
There was blood in a... a few
different places down there.
Before he lost
consciousness.
Logan was moving around.
bleeding everywhere.
It got all over.
Don't worry so much.
Teddy Mac.
Get some sleep.
Big day tomorrow.
Ready?
Good. Just be easy.
Nah. nah. nah. nah. nah.
It ain't like that.
Turn around. Louie.
Unh-unh.
I got somethin'
Claudia gon' want to see.
I doubt that.
Give me the bag.
Hands.
Save you the trouble.
Let's go.
Oh. yeah! Oh. yeah!
Yeah?
That's right. No.
That ain't our problem.
Louie.
Last I remember seeing you.
you spit in my direction
and told me
you wasn't coming back.
My memory of those days is
a little hazy for me. Claudia.
Mine isn't.
You want to introduce me
to your friend?
My nephew... Franklin.
He's cute. Look at that face.
Smooth like polished wood.
Sit down.
How you like my place.
Franklin?
-It's cool.
-Did your auntie tell you
she used to be
a fan favorite up in here?
Till she got a big head.
bit the hand that fed her.
For her to walk you
through my doors.
you must be
in a bad spot.
Maybe she just figured
me and you could be friends.
This how you make friends?
Mm. come on.
I ain't gonna bite.
Ohh!
Unh!
I don't know you. and I feel
like I'm getting played.
We came to deal straight.
Shut the fuck up. Louie.
Taste that.
Let me know how it feel.
Oh. yeah. Yeah.
That's that caviar.
That's the one.
Where'd you get
this shit?
That's my business.
Oh. no. baby boy.
That ain't how it work.
You wanna
walk out of here?
Well. I can't give up my source.
Oh. I think you can.
Here's what I can tell you.
Dude I got that from...
he Israeli.
connected. dangerous.
gave me that bird
on consignment.
-Bullshit.
-It's true.
It's true.
But you're right. Claudia.
I am desperate.
So. the way I figure.
it break down like this.
Buy this key.
and I will bring you
another one tomorrow
and another one
the day after that if you want.
I get a little cash
for my troubles.
you get to have
the purest coke there is.
We both win.
Or you kill us
and take it
and put a crazy Israeli gangster
out 16 G's.
This means he's gonna
come looking for me.
And if I'm dead.
you can be damn sure
he won't stop
till he finds out who did it.
Your nephew's a very impressive
young man. Louie.
16 G's?
And you'll be back here
tomorrow with more?
You staring at that money
like you want to talk dirty to it.
You sure you don't want me
to drive?
Jerome was telling the truth.
you know.
That shit ain't worth
the trouble it come with.
Then why
you bring me in there?
Or what? Let some
Russian gangster kill your ass?
-He Israeli.
-Yeah. whatever he is.
If you smart. you introduce him
to Claudia and get out now.
I do that.
I get nothing.
Nah.
You gon' need it.
No. I won't.
You gon' learn.
one way or the other.
You want
to talk to him?
Go on. baby.
Get out and talk
to your daddy.
Nah.
You sure?
Just drive
the fucking car.